Ashuha Arseniy

Moscow, Russia • 🔊 +7-965-178-2915 • 🖂 ars.ashuha@gmail.com • 🕏 ars-ashuha • k arsashuha • k arsashuha



Summary

I am a second year Master Student at MIPT, I do research at Bayes Group under supervision of prof. Dmitry Vetrov. My research is focused on Bayesian regularization of deep neural nets. At MIPT I work as a teacher assistant for some Machine Learning courses. Also, I am an irregular student of Yandex School of Data Analysis.

Skills: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Bayesian ML, Python, Hadoop, Hive, Linux, English (B2)

Education

| | Bachelor, Computer Science, Bauman Moscow State Technical University, GPA: 3.7/5.0 Identification of unique kernels in topic models, Supervisor: N. Loukachevitch (MSU) | |
|-------------|--|---------------|
| 2015 - 2017 | Master, Machine Learning, Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, GPA: ?/5.0 | \ nass |

Regularization of Deep Neural Nets, Supervisor: Prof. D. Vetrov (HSE), A. Dral (MIPT)

2015 - 2017 Irregular Student, Machine Learning, Yandex School of Data Analysis, GPA: 4.8/5.0 Result Six courses were passed and the favorites are Bayesian Methods, Deep Learning





Publications

Thesis

1. Ashuha A., Loukachevitch N.: Bigramm Anchor Words Topic Model, AIST16

Teaching experience

- 2016 Now: Teacher Assistant, University Course at MIPT, Machine Learning (parts 1,2), ml-mipt.github.io (RU)
- 2016 Now: Teacher Assistant, Additional Course at MIPT, Machine Learning in Action, vk.com/ml_in_action (RU)

Industry experience

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

3 month

Yandex, Moscow — Intern at Music Deep Learning Group

• Searching similar tracks and building recommendation features using DNN



Dec 2013 - Feb 2016

2 year 1 month

Rambler, Moscow — Part-time R&D Engineer at Machine Learning Group

- Improving the quality of classification users using browser history
- Recommendations system for the news posts on rambler.ru
- Optimization performance of users classification
- Application of topic models to building users features

RAMBLER&Co

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013 3 month

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013 | Rambler, Moscow — Intern at Search Group

• Users query classification to display a mixing in search results

RAMBLER&Co

Achievements

• 25.07.2015: I have 2nd place in the the final round and 1st place in the qualifying round at Game. DeepHack